(function(e){function t(t){for(var a,s,i=t[0],u=t[1],l=t[2],d=0,p=[];d<i.length;d++)s=i[d],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(n,s)&&n[s]&&p.push(n[s][0]),n[s]=0;for(a in u)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(u,a)&&(e[a]=u[a]);c&&c(t);while(p.length)p.shift()();return r.push.apply(r,l||[]),o()}function o(){for(var e,t=0;t<r.length;t++){for(var o=r[t],a=!0,i=1;i<o.length;i++){var u=o[i];0!==n[u]&&(a=!1)}a&&(r.splice(t--,1),e=s(s.s=o[0]))}return e}var a={},n={app:0},r=[];function s(t){if(a[t])return a[t].exports;var o=a[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(o.exports,o,o.exports,s),o.l=!0,o.exports}s.m=e,s.c=a,s.d=function(e,t,o){s.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:o})},s.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},s.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=s(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var o=Object.create(null);if(s.r(o),Object.defineProperty(o,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var a in e)s.d(o,a,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,a));return o},s.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return s.d(t,"a",t),t},s.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},s.p="/";var i=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],u=i.push.bind(i);i.push=t,i=i.slice();for(var l=0;l<i.length;l++)t(i[l]);var c=u;r.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),o()})({0:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("56d7")},"034f":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var a=o("85ec"),n=o.n(a);n.a},"56d7":function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);o("e260"),o("e6cf"),o("cca6"),o("a79d");var a=o("2b0e"),n=o("8c4f"),r=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",{attrs:{id:"app"}},[e._m(0),o("form",{attrs:{action:"getFormValues"}},[o("div",{staticClass:"options"},[o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"0"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"0"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"0")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="0"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"0"}},[e._v(" 0 points ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"10"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"10"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"10")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="10"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"10"}},[e._v(" 10 points ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"100"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"100"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"100")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="100"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"100"}},[e._v(" 100 points ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"500"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"500"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"500")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="500"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"500"}},[e._v(" 500 points ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"1000"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"1000"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"1000")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="1000"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"1000"}},[e._v(" 1,000 points ")])]),o("div",{staticClass:"hidden",attrs:{id:"100000"}},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.value,expression:"value"}],attrs:{type:"radio",name:"score",value:"100000"},domProps:{checked:e._q(e.value,"100000")},on:{change:function(t){e.value="100000"}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:"100000"}},[e._v(" 100,000 points ")])])]),o("br"),o("router-link",{attrs:{type:"submit",to:{name:"question",params:{id:e.value}}},nativeOn:{click:function(t){e.routerOpen=!e.routerOpen}}},[e._v("Question Value: "+e._s(e.value.toString().replace(/\B(?=(\d{3})+(?!\d))/g,",")))])],1),o("br"),o("div",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.routerOpen,expression:"routerOpen"}],staticClass:"overlay"},[o("a",{attrs:{href:"/"},on:{click:function(t){e.routerOpen=!e.routerOpen}}},[o("font-awesome-icon",{staticClass:"close",attrs:{icon:"times"}})],1),o("router-view",{directives:[{name:"show",rawName:"v-show",value:e.routerOpen,expression:"routerOpen"}],staticClass:"popup-container"})],1)])},s=[function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("p",[o("b",[e._v("Directions:")]),o("br"),e._v(" -Click and drag to position ball "),o("br"),e._v(" -Click Start Plinko Button"),o("br"),e._v(" -Select the radio button that appears "),o("br"),e._v(" -Click the link ")])}],i=(o("b0c0"),o("ecee")),u=o("c074");i["c"].add(u["a"]);var l={name:"app",data:function(){return{value:10,routerOpen:!1}},methods:{getFormValues:function(e){this.value=e.target.elements.name.value},onClose:function(){this.routerOpen=!1},routerToggle:function(){this.routerOpen=!this.routerOpen}}},c=l,d=(o("034f"),o("2877")),p=Object(d["a"])(c,r,s,!1,null,null,null),h=p.exports,v=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",[o("div",[e._v(" Plinko Board ")]),o("div",[o("div",{staticClass:"score"},[e._v(" Score: "+e._s(e.score)+" ")]),o("div",{staticClass:"button"},[e._v(" Drop Ball ")])])])},m=[],f={data:function(){return{name:"Home",score:1e4}}},w=f,b=Object(d["a"])(w,v,m,!1,null,"d3719648",null),g=b.exports,_=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",[o("div",[o("h1",[e._v("Question:")]),e._v(" Question Num: "+e._s(e.questionNum)+" Value: "+e._s(e.$route.params.id)+" ")]),o("div",[o("div",{staticClass:"question"},[e._v(" "+e._s(e.question)+" "),o("form",[o("div",{staticClass:"options"},e._l(e.options,(function(t,a){return o("div",{key:t,staticClass:"option"},[o("input",{directives:[{name:"model",rawName:"v-model",value:e.answer,expression:"answer"}],attrs:{id:a,name:"option",type:"radio"},domProps:{value:a,checked:e._q(e.answer,a)},on:{change:function(t){e.answer=a}}}),o("label",{attrs:{for:a}},[e._v(e._s(t))])])})),0),o("br"),o("router-link",{attrs:{type:"submit",to:{name:"result",params:{value:this.$route.params.id,qNum:e.questionNum,answer:e.answer}}}},[e._v("Submit Answer: "+e._s(e.answer))])],1)])])])},y=[],q={10:[{question:"What was Play-Doh originally used as?",options:["Eraser","Modeling toy","Wallpaper cleaner","Leak plugger"],answer:"2"},{question:"When were Crocs invented?",options:["1993","2002","1999","1987"],answer:"1"},{question:"Who was the 30th President of the United States?",options:["William Howard Taft","Calvin Coolidge","Herbert Hoover","Grover Cleveland"],answer:"1"},{question:"Do you really want 10 points?",options:["Yes","No ","Maybe","I don't know"],answer:"1"},{question:"What percentage of the final grade is this project worth?\n",options:["15 ","10 ","20 ","25"],answer:"0"},{question:"How many keys are there on a traditional US keyboard?",options:["101 ","103","105","107"],answer:"0"}],100:[{question:"Which of the following is the correct file extension name for JavaScript?",options:[".script",".java",".js",".javascript"],answer:"2"},{question:"What is the language that most websites use for their layout?",options:["HTML ","XHTML","XML","JSON"],answer:"0"},{question:"What programming language is used primarily for relational databases?",options:["SQL","CSS","C#","Python"],answer:"0"},{question:"What JavaScript library have we used to render 3D objects on a web page?",options:["Babylon.js","Vue.js","Node.js","jQuery"],answer:"0"},{question:"What year would a current college freshman with 0 credits graduate if they fell 2 semesters behind?",options:["2023","2024","2022","2025"],answer:"1"},{question:"Who is the current Chancellor of IUPUI?",options:["Mitch Daniels","Nasser Paydar","Michael McRobbie","James Danko"],answer:"1"}],500:[{question:"What Game Show does this game appear on?",options:["Wheel of Fortune","The Price is Right","Hollywood Game Night","Dotto"],answer:"1"},{question:"Who is the current host of this show?",options:["Drew Carey","Patrick Leonard Sajdak","Jack Narz","Jane Lynch"],answer:"0"},{question:"What is the point value of this position squared?",options:["250,000","250.000","25,000","2,500,000"],answer:"0"},{question:"What famous animal was shot and killed on May 28, 2016 after a child got into their enclosure?",options:["Okapi","Koko","Harambe","Clyde"],answer:"2"},{question:"What did Travis Faas write and publish a book on?",options:["Phaser.js","Pixi.js","melonJS","Kiwi.js"],answer:"0"},{question:"Who created the TV series SpongeBob SquarePants?",options:["Michael Dante DiMartino","Butch Hartman","Duncan Rouleau","Stephen Hillenburg"],answer:"3"}],1e3:[{question:"Who created the World Wide Web?",options:["Martin Cooper","Tim Berners-Lee","Henry Sampson","John Logie Baird"],answer:"1"},{question:"When was the World Wide Web created?",options:["1971","1984","1975","1989"],answer:"3"},{question:"What organization creates the standards for the World Wide Web?",options:["Internet Architecture Board","ARINC","W3C","CERN"],answer:"2"},{question:"When did the creator of the World Wide Web die?",options:["April 21, 2016","June 25, 2009","February 11, 2012","They havenâ€™t died yet"],answer:"3"},{question:"Who owns the World Bank?",options:["World Bank Group","International Finance Corporation","World Bank Programme","World Economic Forum"],answer:"0"},{question:"Where is St. Basil's Cathedral located?",options:["Moscow, Russia","London, England","New York City, United States","Reims, France"],answer:"0"}],1e5:[{question:"What percentage of the Earth is covered by water?",options:["83","71 ","64","59"],answer:"1"},{question:"What is the formula for potassium chromate?",options:["K2CrO4 ","K2Cr2O7","C2H3O4","C2H3O2"],answer:"0"},{question:"What is 1 MeV in eV?",options:["2.5721x10^6 eV","1x10^6 eV","1x10^9 eV","2.5721x10^9 eV"],answer:"1"},{question:"Which of the following statements is NOT true regarding the comparison of the alpha-helix structure to the beta-sheet structure in proteins?",options:["The peptide bond in each is planar and trans","Each may occur in typical globular proteins","Each is stabilized by inter-chain hydrogen bonds","All hydrogen bonds between the carbonyl oxygen (C=O) and the amide hydrogen (N-H) are formed in each"],answer:"2"},{question:"What does the word provocados mean in English?",options:["sea crossing","brought about","self-induced abortions","premature newborn"],answer:"2"},{question:"Who coined the term Oedipus Complex?",options:["Sigmund Freud","Lev Vygotsky","Lawrence Kohlberg","Philip Zimbardo"],answer:"0"}],score:0},W={data:function(){var e=Math.floor(6*Math.random());return{answer:"None Yet",questionNum:e,value:this.$route.params.id,question:q[this.$route.params.id][e].question,options:q[this.$route.params.id][e].options}},methods:{}},C=W,k=Object(d["a"])(C,_,y,!1,null,"1952aa5c",null),O=k.exports,S=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",[e._m(0),o("div",{staticClass:"result"},[o("h2",[e._v("Correct: "+e._s(e.result))]),e._v(" The Question: "+e._s(e.question)+" "),o("br"),e._v(" Your Answer: "+e._s(e.useranswer)),o("br"),e._v(" Correct Answer: "+e._s(e.correctanswer)),o("br")]),o("div",{staticClass:"scorecalc"},[o("h2",[e._v("Score")]),e._v(" New Score: "+e._s(e.userScore)),o("br")]),o("div",{staticClass:"button"},[e._v(" Click X to close ")])])},N=[function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",[o("h1",[e._v("Result")])])}],x={data:function(){var e=this.$route.params.qNum,t=this.$route.params.value;return{name:"Result",score:t,result:this.$route.params.answer==q[t][e].answer,question:q[t][e].question,useranswer:q[t][e].options[this.$route.params.answer],correctanswer:q[t][e].options[q[t][e].answer],userScore:q.score}},created:function(){this.$route.params.answer==q[this.score][this.questionNum].answer&&(q.score+=this.$route.params.value)},methods:{}},P=x,j=Object(d["a"])(P,S,N,!1,null,"716c57e6",null),M=j.exports,$=o("ad3d");a["a"].component("font-awesome-icon",$["a"]),a["a"].use(n["a"]);var H=new n["a"]({routes:[{path:"/",component:g},{path:"/question/:id",component:O,name:"question"},{path:"/question",component:O},{path:"/result/:value/:qNum/:answer",component:M,name:"result"},{path:"/result",component:M}]});new a["a"]({router:H,render:function(e){return e(h)}}).$mount("#app")},"85ec":function(e,t,o){}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.403a8198.js.map